(Penny:)Sheldon, honey, I've told you,
it's a small apartment.
(Penny:)- You only have to knock one...
- I don't have a lot of time.
(Sheldon:)Look, Ramona finally dozed off,
and I need you to help me get rid of her.
(Penny:)Get rid of her how?
(Sheldon:)I don't know, but, apparently,
I'm in some kind of relationship...
...and, well, you seem to be an expert
at ending them.
(Ramona:)Excuse me?
(Sheldon:)I see man after man
leaving this apartment never to return.
(Penny:)Okay, first of all, it is not man after man.
RAMONA: Dr. Cooper?
- Hide me.
- Hide you?
- I formally request sanctuary.
(Ramona:)Why aren't you working?
(Leonard:)Um...
(Sheldon:)She distracted me.
(Sheldon:)I told you,
I don't have time for your nonsense.
(Sheldon:)I have important things to do.
- Oh, man.
- I know what's going on here.